

RYAN ADI SAPUTRA

Hello everyone!

My name is Ryan. I am from Indonesia. I am a college student majoring in software engineering. I am very enthusiastic about software development and UI/UX design. Gradually gaining experience and structuring my knowledge.I always feel challenged to work and learn on new projects and I am very dedicated to my work.

CURRICULUM VITAE

SKILLS

digital

Adobe photoshop

Adobe illustrator

UI/UX design

Figma

software development

Git

Web development

personal

Personal qualities
Self-organization
Team work
Creativity
Communication

Determination

CONTACTS

email riyanadi552@gmail.com

phone number +62 838 7753 4525

discord lolajayakan#4169

instagram
instagram.com/iniryanaja

linkedin

linkedin.com/in/ryan-adi-0b058b1b3

github

github.com/iniryan

website iniryan.github.io

EDUCATION

2018 - 2021

SMK NEGERI 4 MALANG Software engineering

2021 - present

Institut Teknologi Telkom Surabaya Software engineering

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 - June 2020

Ministry of State Secretariat RI Graphic designer and IT support

July 2020 - Dec 2020

PT. Mejakita Edunusa Mandiri UI/UX designer

ORGANIZATION

2018 - 2019

BDI SMK NEGERI 4 MALANG

Event and documentation division

2020

OSD Creative

Front-end developer and UI/UX designer